ILGWU Political Department, Evelyn Dubrow Papers 5780/119
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Northeast Department, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Puerto Rico, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Southeast Region, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Upper South Department, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Western States Region, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- January, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- February, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- March, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- April, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- May, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- June, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- July, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- August, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- September, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- October, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- November, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- December, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- "A" General, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO General, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO Cope General, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- AFL-CIO Statements, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Cope - Political Memo, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- AFL-CIO IUD General, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- AFL-CIO News (Mimeo), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Civil Rights, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Coalition for a Democratic Majority, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Conference of Women in Industry, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Congress, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Consumer Assembly, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Consumers Legislation, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Convention Report, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Convention Report, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Democratic National Committee, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- "D" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Democratic Charter Committee, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Democratic Study Group, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Evelyn Dubrow Expenses, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- "E" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Economic Stabilization Act, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- "F" General, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Facts About Congress, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Frontlash, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- "G" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- "H" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- "I" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Health (General), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Health Security, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Impoundment of Funds, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- "J" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- "K" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- "L" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Labor - General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- League of Women Voters, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Evelyn Dubrow Lobbying Reports, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- "M" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Minimum Wage, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Reports from Locals on Minimum Wage Campaign, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- "N" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- National Consumers League, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- National Sharecroppers, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- "P" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Pension Legislation, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Pension Reform Bill, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Rural Development Acts Grant, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- "R" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Senate - General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- "S" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- "T" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Trade, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- "U" General, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Visitors to Israel Program, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Pacelli D'Antona, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Catastrophic Illness, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 50)